Guide to the Philip Agee Papers TAM.517
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series VI, Subject Files
  - Subseries VI-D, Individuals, Organizations, Topics
    - World Bank: International Monetary Fund, 1979, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - World Service Authority, 1981-1991 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - World Service Authority: "Passports", 1990 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - World Trade Center 9/11 (Clippings), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Series VII, University Lectures, Teaching and Research Files
  Series VII, University Lectures, Teaching and Research Files (1948-1999) contains lectures and resarch materials for his talks and courses. Topics include U.S. foreign intelligence activity, the extreme right in Europe, including the activities of former Nazis in Germany, and files on a course "Reinhard Gehlen (a Nazi who collaborated with U.S. intelligence agencies) and the Continuation of the German War against the USSR." Agee taught most frequently in Europe, and within Europe, in both West and East Germany, and some of the materials are in German.
  - "The Central Intelligence Agency, The Cold War and Right Wing Extremism" Lecture (Introduction to the Seminar) and Bibliography (English, German), Aug 1995 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - "The Central Intelligence Agency, The Cold War and Right Wing Extremism," Syllabus and Bibliography (English, German), Winter 1995 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - "Christian Identity in the US" (Research Materials, Nov 1, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Class at Alliance Francaise, undated (Box 15, Folder 37a)
  - Cold War, Late 1940's: Lecture and Research Materials (English, German), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Cold War, Late 1940's: Reading Assignments, 1967-1993 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - "Denazification of Germany and the United States:" Lecture (English, German), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - "Denazification of Germany and the United States:" Reading Assignments, undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - "Denazification of Germany and the United States:" Research Materials, undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - "European Parliamentary Debates: 1985, 1991, 1993," Reading Assignments, 1985-1993 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - "The Extreme Right in Europe in the 1990s:" Lecture (English, German), Jul 1993 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - "The Extreme Right in Europe in the 1990s," Research Materials, 1985-1991 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - "The Extreme Right in the US and Canada in the 1990s:" Lecture (English, German), undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Foreign Intelligence: Resources for Teaching and Research, 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Greece: Lecture (English, German) and Research Materials, 1992-1997 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Greece: Security Battallions (1941-1944); US Intervention (1947-1974): Reading Assignments, 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Guatemala, Lecture and Research Materials, 1994-1997 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Hamburg University: Contracts, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Hamburg University: "Hamburg Program"-Study Abroad for Cornell, Indiana, Ohio State, Temple, Tulane, Purdue University, University of Kansas, and Smith College, 1994-1997 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Hamburg University: Phillip Agee's Request for Financial Support for Research, Writing, and University Teaching, May 1995 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Hamburg University: Students (Agee's Evaluations, Notes, Office Hour Sign-Ups), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Italy-1948 Elections and the CIA: Lecture (English, German) and Research Materials, 1976, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Italy-Role of P-2, 1994 Elections Neonazism: Reading Assignments, 1985-1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Italy-US Intervention in 1947-1948, 1960s and 1970s, and Gladio Reading Assignments, 1978-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "Nationalism as a 'Communist Treat' and Military Dictatorship as the Solution: Iran, Guetamala and Indonesia:" Lectures (English, German), undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Neo-Nazism and Racism in America" Research Materials, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - "Neo-Nazism in Germany" Research Materials (English), 1990s (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - "Neo-Nazism in Germany" Research Materials (German), 1990s (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "The Philippines: Containment, Control, Dictatorship, and Death Squads:" Lectures (English, German)8, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "The Philippines: Containment, Control, Dictatorship, and Death Squads" Research Materials, 1990-1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "Reorganization of National Security, 1950s," Lecture (English, German), Reading Assignments, Research Materials, 1948, 1976, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Origins of the Cold War:" Lecture (English, German), undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Racism, Anti-Semitism, Homophobia:" Reading Assignments, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "Racism, Anti-Semitism, Homophobia" Research Materials, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "Refuges and Ratlines:" Reading Assignments, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - "Reinhard Gehlen and Continuation of the German War against the USSR:" Lecture (English, German), undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - "Reinhard Gehlen and Continuation of the German War against the USSR" Reading Assignments, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - "Reinhard Gehlen and Continuation of the German War against the USSR:" Research Materials, 1971-1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Seminar Outlines, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Syllabi by Other Lecturers, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Vietnam: Lecture (German), undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Series VIII, Writings
  Series VIII, Writings (1974-2007) includes published writings, including "Phillip Agee's Peregrinations-His Account," "Gulf War Launches New World Order," and book reviews; unpublished Writings, including the book-length "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," and "The Blond Who Spied on Me"; interviews with Agee (press, radio, documentary); speeches, including several on Latin America; reviews of Agee's writings; writings about Agee; and writings by others that were of interest to Agee.
  - Subseries VIII-A, Published Writings
    - "The CIA's Blueprint for Nicaragua" (English, Spanish), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Clippings (English), 1974-1987, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Clippings (Foreign), 1979-1984 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - "'Comments on Yankee Sandinistas' by Ron Ridenour", 1986 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - "Exposing the CIA," Chapter of Dirty Work, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - "Gulf War Launches 'New World Order'", Mar 1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - "Introduction: Where Myths Lead to Murder" in Dirty Work, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Letters to the Editors (Manuscripts, Typescripts), 1976-1981, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - "Liberté, Égalité, Torture"-Book Review of "Torture: The Role of Ideology in the French-Algerian War", 1990, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - "Phillip Agee's Peregrinations-His Account" in Peoples News Service (Includes other News Re. Nazi Groups, Irish Prisoners), 1978 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Subseries VIII-B, Unpublished Writings
    - "After 500 Years: More of the Same?", undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - "Agee Reflects on his Troubles" (English Manuscript of Dutsch Article Published in VRIJ Nederland", 1978 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - "America's Continuing Cold War Against Cuba", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - "The 'American Factor' in Greece: Old and New", Apr 1976 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - "The Blond Who Spied on Me" (Janet Strickland alias Leslie Donegan, includes Clipping), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - "Bringing in the Coffee-Nicaragua's Wartime Harvest", 1984 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - "Changes in CIA Personnel between August 1975 and July 1976", undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - CIA (Untitled Manuscripts), 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - The CIA at Fifty, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers on What the CIA does and Why," Introduction, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 2. Peace Movement and 3. Freeze Campaign (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 4. Accuracy of Information (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 5. White Houses Policies, undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 6. Production of Information, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 7. Intelligence on the Soviets (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 8. Reagan Certifications on El Salvador, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 8A. CIA and the Soviet Union (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 9. CIA Report on El Salvador, undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 10. Counterintelligence Failures, undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 11. President's Involvement in International Conflicts, undated (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 12. Post World War II, Cold War, and Soviet Expansion (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 13. Truman Doctrine, Containment, Greece, undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 14. Marshall Plan and Western Europe, undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 15. The Berlin Blockade and the Danger of Soviet Invasion in Western Europe, undated (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 16. Foreign Politics Preceding the National Security Report '68 (NSR-68, includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 17. The Office of Police Coordination and the Soviet Union (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 18. CIA's "Suicide Missions" in Eastern Europe, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 19. Radio Free Europe and the Hungarian Revolution of 1956, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 20. Soviet Activities Against Washington, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 21. Secret Political Operations Outside of the US (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 22. CIA's Involvement in Assassinations (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 22A. US Foreign Policy in Third World Countries (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 23. CIA's Propaganda in Western Europe (includes Research Materials) (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 24. American News Organizations' Involvement with CIA, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 25. CIA and Youth Organizations, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 27. CIA and Churches and Religious Groups, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 28. Trade Unions Financed by the CIA (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 29. US Institutes and Foundations, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 30. The Role of the International Trade Secretariats in CIA Operations (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 31. Effectiveness of the CIA, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 32. Proprietaries and Payments, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 33. International Drug Trade, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 34. Operations with Refugees, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 35. Paramilitary Operations-Nicaragua, Angola, Indonesia, Etc. (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 36. Counter-Insurgency Operations in Southeast Asia, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 37. CIA's Relation to Guerrilla Movements, Death Squads, Disappearances, Torture (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - "The CIA for Beginners: 100 Questions and Answers," 38. Terrorism and Antiterrorism (includes Research Materials), undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - "The CIA, Human Rights, and American Democracy", undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - "The CIA in Post-Bishop Grenada", 1983 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - "The CIA in Western Europe", 1982 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - "The CIA Labor Operations in Britain", undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - "The CIA's War Against Che Guevara", 1997 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - The CIA's War Against Cuba and Cuba's Response (English, German), Feb 1994 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - "Commentary for La Republica (Rome) on Leaked Document Giving US Embassy Evaluation of Anti-Terrorist Agencies", Feb 1979 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - "Deportation-Four Years Later", undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - "Destabilization in Jamaica", 1980 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - "Exposing the Constitution", Aug 1989 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - "Five Years Later: Return of the Free Wheeling CIA", Summer 1979 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - "Goodbye, Bruce Hitchens" (Chapter of "Dirty Work"), 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - "Foreword for Publication of the CIA's 'Psychological Operations in Guerrilla Warfare and the Freedom Fighter's Manual'", 1985 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - "A Friendly Interview" (About Robert Deindorfer), undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - "Glasnost -Casey Style", Nov 1987 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - "Inside the Company: CIA Diary-Introduction to Swedish Population", undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - "Introduction-Che" (Biography), circa 1990 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - "The Invisible Hand in Mexico", undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - "How the Director of Central Intelligence Projected US Activities for 1976-1981" (Introductory Statement), undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - "Keepin' On" (Manuscript for the Rolling Stones) with Editor's Introduction, undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - "Letter from Amsterdam" Re. British Expulsion, undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - "Mexico: The Campaign Goes Public", Oct 3, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - "My Stake in Jamaica's Elections", Aug 1980 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - "Naming Names-Why?", 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - "Nicaragua Revisited-1983" (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Open Letter To Admirable Stan Turner, Oct 22, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 49A)
    - "Panama: Only the Latest and Not the Last", undated (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - "The Patriots" (Co-Authored by Steve Weissman, undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - "A Personal Reflection on Ernesto Che Guevara", 2007 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - "The Politics of Conspiracy-Introduction", undated (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - "Pike Report-Introduction", Aug 1976 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - "Prologue for Por Qué Carlos" (Assassination of Cuban Exile Carlos Muñiz Varela), undated (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - "Radio Free Europe and Radio Liberty", undated (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - "Revelations, Investigations, and Reforms of the American Security Services-Where Do We Go from Here?", undated (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - "Robert Moss's Obsession", undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - "The Rockefeller Report: A Partial Victory", Jul 1975 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - "Ronald Reagan-Corporate America's Joseph Goebbels", 1983 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Special Introduction to the Spanish Edition of "Inside the Company: CIA Diary", Dec 1977 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Special Introduction to 1992 Edition of CIA Intern: Tagebuch 1956-1974 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - "Spying on Your Allies: Another Embarrassment for American Intelligence" (US Espionage in Italy), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Statement about a Proposed Data Processing Project Concerning the US Central Intelligence, Undated (Box 17, Folder 63A)
    - Statement: Agee's Announcement of a "New Campaign to Fight the US CIA" (Includes "List of CIA People in Mexico City"), undated (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Synopsis for a Book on the Politics of the Agee/Hosenball Deportations, undated (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - "Thoughts on the New World Disorder", Oct 1993 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - "The Trial of the Red Army Fraction-Modern Democracy, German Style" (Article Proposal), undated (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - "Uncloaking the CIA", 1985 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - "U.S. Covert Operations for the 1990s", 1992 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - "U.S. Democracy-At Home and Abroad", Jun 1992 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - "The US Intelligence System", 1979 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - "United States Policies for the Manipulation of Foreign Civil Societies as Applied in Cuba" (Paper at 2004 Habana, Oct 18-20, 2004), Oct 18, 2004-Oct 20, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Untitled Manuscripts, 1977, undated (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Untitled Manuscript, Chapter 1: "The Real Meaning of 'Containment'", undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Untitled Manuscript, Chapter 2: "Rollback, Not Just Containment", undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Untitled Manuscript Chapter 4: "Vietnam Everything for a Losing Cause", undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Untitled Manuscript, Chapter 5: "Nationalism as a 'Communist Threat' and Military Dictatorship as Solution, Iran, Guetamala, and Indonesia (Includes Research Materials), 1984-1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - "Watch Your Language, Americans-And Your Passports, Too.", undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - "Why the CIA Should Be Exposed?", 1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - "A Woman in the Grenadian Nightmare: An Interview with Regina Fuchs, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Der CIA auf Grenanda nach dem Tode Maurice Bishops", Jan 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - "Comentarios de Phillip Agee Evento de Solidaridad Con los Cinco Cubanos Presos en Los Estados Unidas," Madrid, 21 de Octubre de 2006, Oct 21, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "La Crisis del Golfo y la Guerra Fria", undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Subseries VIII-C, Interviews
    - Interviews: Clippings (English), 1975-1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Interviews: Manuscripts (English), 1975-1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Interviews: Clippings (English), 1974-1977,1984-1992 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Interviews (Finnish, Swedish), 1979-1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Interviews (Dutch), 1975-1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Interviews (French), 1975-1982 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Interviews (German), 1975-1987, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Interviews (Portuguese), 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Interviews (Russian), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Interviews (Spanish), 1974-1988, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Interview for French Documentary (Untitled, English Transcript), undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Interviews: Invoices and Correspondence, 1975-1976, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Interview on National Radio WBAI FM 99.5, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Interviews: Radio, Television Transcripts, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Subseries VIII-D, Speeches
    - "The Gulf Crisis and the Cold War", 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - "Producing the Proper Crisis", Nov 1990 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Remarks by Phillip Agee on Fundraising Tour for Maurice Bishop and Martyrs of October 19, 1983 Memorial Foundation (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Speech on El Salvador (German), undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Statement from Phillip Agee for June 1 PAM Meeting, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Public Meeting at Central Hall, Westminster, Speeches by Ramsey Clark, Morton Halperin, Mel Wulf on Agee's Deportation, Feb 4, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Subseries VIII-E, Reviews of Agee's Writings
    - Book Announcements, Advertisements: "Inside the Company-CIA Diary", 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Book Reviews: "Dirty Work", 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Book Reviews-Inside the Company: CIA Diary, Mar 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Book Reviews-Inside the Company: CIA Diary, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Book Reviews-Inside the Company: CIA Diary (Photocopies), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Book Reviews-Inside the Company: CIA Diary, Jul 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Book Reviews-Inside the Company: CIA Diary, Jan-Feb 1975 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Book Reviews-Inside the Company: CIA Diary, July 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Book Reviews-Inside the Company: CIA Diary, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Book Reviews-Inside the Company: CIA Diary (Foreign), 1975-1984 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Book Reviews: "On the Run", 1987 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Book Reviews: "On the Run" (Dutch), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Book Reviews: "On the Run" (Spanish Acoso Y Fuga), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Book Review: "White Paper, Whitewash", 1981 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Book Reviews: Other Books, 1974-1999 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Subseries VIII-F, Writings About Agee
    - Allegations re. Agee and the Soviet Union, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - CIA: Crisis After Agee's Exposure of Names and Operations, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - CIA in Columbia, Dec 1974 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - CIA in Cuba, 1974-1981 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - CIA in El Salvador, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - CIA in Guyana, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Exposure of CIA Agents, Great Britain, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Exposure of CIA Agents, Jamaica, 1976-1999 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Greene, Graham; Book Review; Chicago Sun-Times, April 17, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Halperin, Morton: Attorney of ACLU, Nominee for Pres. Clinton's Assistant Secretary of Defense for Democracy and Peacekeeping, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Institute for Policy Studies; Relationship with Philip Agee, Communism, Cuba, etc., April 9, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - "Intelligence Identities Protection Act", 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Iran-Connections with Agee, Dec 17, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Latin America (General), CIA, 1974-1981, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Lecture Tour to the US, 1987, Jun 1987-Nov 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Lecture Tour to the US, 1988, Mar 1988-Nov 1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Lecture Tour to the US, 1989, Mar 1989-Nov 1989 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Lecture Tour to the US, 1991, Apr 1991-Nov 1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Topics, US Sources, undated, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Topics, US Sources, 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Topics, US Sources, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Topics, US Sources, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Topics, US Sources, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Topics, US Sources, 1994-1997, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Topics (Arabic), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Topics (Danish), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Topics (Dutch), 1974-1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Topics (Finnish), 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Topics (French), 1974-1984 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Topics (German), 1975-1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)